thegoodride.com 2018-08-27

# Privacy Policy of thegoodride.com

AvantLink has created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our commitment to the privacy and protection of your information. As part of the normal operation of services, we collect, retain, protect and, in some instances, disclose information about you. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. By using the Site, or affiliating with the Network, either as an Affiliate or Merchant, you are accepting the terms of this Privacy Policy and you are consenting to the Network’s practices outlined herein. Any defined term used herein, but not defined herein, shall have the meaning ascribed to the term in the Terms of Use.

1\. Information Collected During Your Use of the AvantLink Service

In order to register as an Affiliate or Merchant, Users are required to provide contact information(e.g., your name and email address), unique identifiers (e.g., your password), and demographic information (e.g., your zip code). Certain information, such as passwords and email addresses, is collected in order to verify your identity to access our services and is stored in our systems. Other information is provided to verify your identity and allow for proper communications and business dealings between the Network, Affiliates and Merchants.

2\. Our Use of User/Client Information

We may use your personal information from any registration form for our legitimate business interests including some or all of the following reasons: to send Users information about product updates, alerts and other service announcements. We may use your IP address to help protect each party against fraud. We will retain all of this information in Network databases only for as long as it is necessary and relevant to comply with the Terms of Use or any Merchant Agreement, Merchant Program, governmental investigation, or other such proceeding.

3\. Our use of Consumer Information collected via our campaign tracking system

We may process your personal information such as IP address, web browser and device information for our legitimate business interests. These legitimate business interests include accurate sales referral tracking data, fraud prevention and network security. We will retain all of this information in Network databases only for as long as it is necessary and relevant to comply with the Terms of Use or any Merchant Agreement, Merchant Program, governmental investigation, or other such proceeding.

4\. Cookies

We also collect and store certain types of information when you interact with us by using “cookies” and logs, which are tools that obtain information from your Internet device as you access AvantLink and/or our ad campaign tracking system. These cookies are used for legitimate business interests as stated in Section 2 and 3 of this Privacy Policy as well as to help us improve your user experience and to ensure we are able to provide you with the best service possible.

5\. Personal Information access, correction, deletion and blockage

You have the right of access to your personal data at any time and may demand correction.

You have the right to object to this processing of personal information if you wish.

If you are registered as an Affiliate or Merchant client, you may access your personal information via your account interface and modify/update the data yourself.

If additional help is needed to access, modify, delete or block personal information, please email privacy@avantlink.com

6\. Our Disclosure of Your Information

We never use or share the personally identifiable information, provided to us online, in ways unrelated to the ones described in this Privacy Policy and without also providing you an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses, except as provided below. Personally identifiable information required to be shared with Merchants for any Merchant Programs Affiliates join, will be communicated to Merchants for purposes of verifying and transmitting commissions. AvantLink will never willfully sell, lease, or rent any of your or your business' personally identifiable information to any third party.

7\. Security

In order to maximize the protection of your information, AvantLink uses state-of-the-art technology to protect your data from use, misuse, or alteration by unauthorized third parties. Currently, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol to protect your data and secure your transactions. SSL encrypts all your personal information, including your credit card number, name, and address, as it is transmitted over the Internet. Your data is protected through reasonable and appropriate security measures, including but not limited to logical access restrictions, physical hardware and security restrictions, network restrictions, system access restrictions, and the principle of least privilege.

8\. Amendments

AvantLink reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy to keep up with new laws and regulations or if we determine that amendments are required for other reasons. The date of the latest amendment will be posted at the bottom of this policy.

9\. General

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the AvantLink Terms of Use.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement or the practices of this Site, please contact us at privacy@avantlink.com

Last Amended: May 15th, 2018
